copperchef.com 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy | Tristarproductsinc

Welcome to this website owned and operated by Tristar Products, Inc. and its affiliates and/or subsidiaries ("Tristar Products"). Tristar Products is pleased to offer its products, and provide other related information and materials to you through the website that directed you to this page. Because your privacy is important to us, we provide this notice explaining our online practices and your choices regarding our use of information about you collected through this website. This Notice applies only to the information collected by Tristar Products from the users of our website. 

**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT.** To enable you to participate in our site offerings and fulfill your request for products and services, we may collect certain personally identifiable information, including contact information such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as payment information (e.g. credit card numbers and billing address). We may collect information about your interest in and use of our products and services.

In addition, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website, such as the domain name of your Internet service provider, type of browser you are using, and the type of operating system you are using. 

**2\. HOW WE USE INFORMATION.** We use the information you provide to fulfill your requests for our products and service (e.g., send you the product you requested), respond to your questions, improve our Web page content, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We also may use personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of our products or services, changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use, or other policies or terms that affect you and the use of our website or our products and services. In addition, we may use such information to improve the content and navigation of our website, or for other internal purposes.

We may use the services of agents and contractors to assist us in providing our products and services.

We may share personally identifiable information with unrelated third parties (e.g., other marketers) to enable them to provide users with opportunities to learn about products or services in which they may be interested. Please see the "Your Choices" section below for more information on how you can express your preferences regarding our sharing of information.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process (e.g., a court order or a subpoena) or comply with legal requirements. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.

In addition, we may disclose anonymous, aggregated user statistics to third parties for a variety of purposes. For example, we may disclose how many individuals visited certain areas of our website, how many men or women purchase a particular product, or other demographic data about users of our products or services.

**3\. YOUR CHOICES.** As noted above, we may use the personally identifiable information we collect from you to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like to opt out of future promotional materials from us, you may indicate this preference by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of e-mail communications or by contacting us at [_**unsubscribe@tristarproductsinc.com**_](mailto:unsubscribe@tristarproductsinc.com). Please note that even if you opt out of promotional messages from us, we will continue to send you important account-related information.

If you would like to request that we not share your information for such purposes, please send us an e-mail at 

[_**unsubscribe@tristarproductsinc.com**_](mailto:unsubscribe@tristarproductsinc.com).

**4\. HOW WE USE COOKIES.** To enhance your experience with our site, our Web pages may use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site[s]. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our site[s]. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may contract with third-party vendors, who act on our behalf, to serve ads to our customers via the internet or to send directly to customers whom we think may be interested in our products or services. To do this, the vendors will collect anonymous information about your visits to our website and your interaction with our products and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of the cookie or pixel tag – industry standard technology used by most major websites. They may also pool the anonymous information that they collect with other sources of information not collected during your visit to our website, which may include your name and mailing address, for purposes of determining whether you might be interested in receiving direct mail.

If you do not wish for cookies or pixel tags to be placed on your computer, most commercially available Web browsers permit you to modify your preferences to prevent that from taking place. To opt-out of receiving our direct mail, you may send us an email at 

[_**privacy@tristarproductsinc.com**_](mailto:privacy@tristarproductsinc.com) or call us at [_**973-287-5134**_](tel://1-973-287-5134).

**5\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES.** We sometimes may offer content (e.g., promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with an identified third party. In these instances, the third party may obtain information that you voluntarily submit to participate in a site activity. We have no control over the third party's use of this information. The site will notify you at the time of information collection if a third party will obtain such information.

In addition, our site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

**6\. DATA SECURITY.** We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our websites, and you do so at your own risk.

**7\. UPDATES.** We may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of material changes to our Privacy Policy by placing a notice on our website. Please check back to this policy statement at our website to learn what information we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it.

**8\. HOW TO CONTACT US.** If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please e-mail at [_**privacy@tristarproductsinc.com**_](mailto:privacy@tristarproductsinc.com) or write us at **Tristar Products Inc. 492 Route 46 East, Fairfield, NJ 07004**.
